Update is probably the most commonly
Update 関数は、Unity で最も頻繁に使用されるであろう
used function in Unity.
関数です。
It's called once per frame on every script
この関数を使用する場合は、毎フレームごとに
that uses it. Almost anything that needs
コールされます。定期的なタイミングで
to be changed or adjusted regularly happens here.
変更、または調整する必要がある処理を、ここで実行します。
The movement of non-physics objects,
物理挙動のないオブジェクトの動作や
simple timers and the detection of input
簡単なタイマー、さらには入力の検知は
are just a few things that are usually
Update 関数の中で行われる
done in update. Note that update is not
処理です。Update はコールされる間隔が完全に一定ではないことを
called on a regular timeline. If one frame
覚えておくべきです。もし 1 フレームを処理するのが
takes longer to process than the next
次のフレームを処理する時間より長い場合は
then the time between update calls will
Update 関数がコールされる間隔は
be different. Fixed update is a similar
違ってきます。 FixedUpdate 関数は似たような関数ですが
function to update but it has a few
重要な違いがいくつか
important differences. Fixed update is
あります。FixedUpdate 関数は
called on a regular timeline and will have
定期的なサイクルで処理が行われるものであり、
the same time between calls.
コールされる間隔が完全に一定です。
Immediately after fixed update is called,
FixedUpdate がコールされた直後、
any necessary physics calculations are made.
必要な物理計算がすべて行われます。
As such anything that effects a rigidbody -
このため、Rigidbody に影響するすべてのこと、
meaning a physics object, should be executed
すなわち 物理挙動のあるオブジェクトは、
in fixed update rather than update.
Update 関数ではなく FixedUpdate 関数で実行すべきです。
When scripting physics in the fixed update
FixedUpdate により物理挙動のスクリプトを書く場合、
it's good practice to use forces for movement.
動作については、 Force を使うべきです。
Let's take a look at the difference
それでは FixdUpdate と Update コールの違いを
between fixed update and update calls.
見ていくことにします。
In this example we're logging to the console
このサンプルでは、すべての FixedUpdate および Update ごとに
with each fixed update and update by adding
コンソール出力を行うために
the value of Time.deltaTime.
Time.deltatime を使用します。
When I press play
これでゲーム再生を行って
and pause
ポーズをすれば
you can see that the time between fixed
FixedUpdate の間の間隔はつねに 0.02 であることが
updates is always 0.02.
確認できます。
where the time between updates varies.
一方で Update の間の間隔は変化します。
This can be shown even more clearly by
これはコンソール ウィンドウを展開することで
collapsing the console.
より顕著になります。
If I play now and pause
ここでゲーム再生を行ってポーズをすれば
you can see that all of my fixed updates
すべての FixedUpdate は一行にまとめられる
are collapsed in to one. There's been 111
ことが確認できます。 111 個が 1 行にまとめられ
of them and they're all 0.02.
すべて 0.02 の間隔で行われてます。
Whereas the update times vary.
Update の間隔は変化しています。 (翻訳:gamesonytablet)